Guide to the Wunderman Archives, 1946-2010 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Account Files, 1964-2001 and undated, (126 boxes)
  - Columbia House
    - Account Files
      - CDHQ, 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box AF50)
      - Creative (English and French), 1996 (Box AF50)
      - Creative by music genre, 1995 (Box AF50)
      - Columbia Video Game Club, 1983-1984 (Box AF50)
      - Play, 1996 (Box AF50)
      - Storyboards, 1984-1991 (Box AF50)
      - Strategies for Managing Leadership, 1995 (Box AF50)
    - Mailings, 1979-1995, (5 folders) (Box AF50)
    - Print advertising, 1985-1994, (6 folders) (Box AF51)
  - Comcast
    - Five Star Festival, 1997 (Box AF51)
  - Concord Credit
    - Mailing, undated (Box AF51)
  - Consumer Credit Counseling Service
    - Advertising, 1997-1998 (Box AF51)
    - Clippings, 1999-2000 (Box AF51)
  - Credit Card Service Bureau (CCSB/Visa)
    - General files, 1979 and undated (Box AF51)
  - Debt Counsellors of America
    - Self-Help, 1997-1999 (Box AF51)
  - De Kuyper (Chicago)
    - Point-of-consumption creative, 1998 (Box AF51)
  - Dell (Miami)
    - Miscellaneous (English and Spanish), 1995-1996 (Box AF51)
  - Digital PC
    - Advertising (Spanish), 1994 (Box AF51)
  - Discovery Channel (Miami)
    - Eco-Challenge booklet, 1999 (Box AF52)
  - Disney
    - Club Disney, 1996-1997, (3 folders) (Box AF52)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box AF52)
  - Dow Jones Newswires
    - Creative, 1997 (Box AF52)
    - Printed material, 1998 (Box AF52)
  - DuPont
    - Archivek, undated (Box FA53)
    - Brazil, creative, 1992 (Box FA53)
    - Case studies, 1985-1996, (2 folders) (Box FA53)
    - Chicago--J.C. Penney/Lycra 9-2-5 launch, 1996 (Box FA53)
    - Comforel, 1995 (Box FA53)
    - Detroit--Automotive, 1995 (Box FA53)
    - Kevlar, 1990-1996 (Box FA53)
    - Lycra, 1996-1997 (Box FA53)
    - Mailings, 1989-1996 (Box FA53)
    - Mylar RL, undated (Box AF54)
    - Miscellaneous creative, 1996 and undated (Box AF54)
    - Printed materials, 1990-1996 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF54)
    - Tyvek, 1990-1998, (7 folders) (Box AF54)
    - Vespel, 1989 (Box AF54)
  - Edison Source
    - Mailer, undated (Box AF55)
  - Ericsson
    - Channel Marketing Toolbox (Malmo meeting), 1997 (Box AF55)
    - Current Channel Marketing Activities Within Ericsson Mobile Communications, 1997 (Box AF55)
    - Ericsson Cup tennis tournament (Spanish), 1997, (2 folders) (Box AF55)
    - James Bond tie-in and sweepstakes, 1997 (Box AF55)
    - Point of sale creative, 1998 (Box AF55)
    - Printed material (Spanish and Portuguese), 1997-1998 (Box AF55)
    - Take Five! Segmentation brochure, 1995 (Box AF55)
  - Fila Fitness
    - Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box AF55)
  - Flintstones Vitamins
    - Creative and case studies, 1995 (Box AF55)
  - Ford Motor Company
    - Account Files
      - General files, 1982-1992, (4 folders) (Box AF56)
      - Award entry, World awards, 1988 (Box AF56)
      - Case studies, 1992-1997, (2 folders) (Box AF56)
      - Chicago--Mercury Cycling Team, 1997 (Box AF56)
      - Detroit (Box AF56)
      - Lincoln Navigator, 1997
        - Lincoln Town Car, 1997 (Box AF57)
      - Mercury Grand Marquis, 1997 (Box AF57)
      - Mercury Sable, 1995 (Box AF57)
      - Fulfillment items, undated (Box AF57)
      - Germany--Ka model creative (English, Spanish, German), 1995-1997 (Box AF57)
      - Greece--Fleet Division (Greek), 1996 (Box AF57)
      - Irvine--Lincoln, 1991-1997 (Box AF57)
      - Lincoln booklet, 1998 (Box AF57)
      - Lincoln Continental launch, 1995 (Box AF57)
      - Merkur XR4Ti Challenge (Box AF57)
      - Reports and miscellaneous, 1987-1999 and undated (Box AF57)
      - QCP Standards, 1995 (Box AF57)
      - Scorpio, 1987-1988 (Box AF57)
      - Spain--Escort product guide (Spanish), 1997 (Box AF57)
      - United Kingdom mailer, undated (Box AF57)
      - Visteon (English, French, German), 1997 (Box AF57)
      - WCJ Ford Story, 1997 (Box AF57)
    - Mailings
      - 30-Day/9 month owners, 1988 (Box AF58)
      - 30-42 months of ownership, 1989 (Box AF58)
      - American Road, 1994 (Box AF58)
      - Car Buying Made Easier, 1986-1990 (Box AF58)
      - Financing, 1986 (Box AF58)
      - Ford Collection, 1986 (Box AF58)
      - Ford consumer finance home equity solicitation, 1990 (Box AF58)
      - Ford Update, 1991-1994 (Box AF58)
      - Images (photographs by notable photographers), undated (Box AF58)
      - Leasing, 1990 (Box AF58)
      - Legend of Lincoln, 1986 (Box AF58)
      - Lincoln Commitment, 1991 (Box AF58)
      - Lincoln Continental, 1995 (Box AF58)
      - Lincoln Mark VIII, 1997 (Box AF58)
      - Lincoln-Mercury, 1988-1992, (1 of 2 folders) (Box AF58)
      - Lincoln-Mercury, 1988-1992 (continued), (2 of 2 folders) (Box AF59)
      - Lincoln to dissatisfied Cadillac owners, 1983 (Box AF59)
      - Lincoln Update, 1991-1993 (Box AF59)
      - Mercury, 1997 (Box AF59)
      - Mercury Sable, 1999, (2 folders) (Box AF59)
      - Mercury trivia, 1986 (Box AF59)
      - Mercury Update, 1991-1993 (Box AF59)
      - Miscellaneous, 1994-1997 (Box AF59)
      - Non-responder, 1989-1990 (Box AF59)
      - Series reports, 1989 (Box AF59)
    - Printed material
      - Annual Report, 1995 (Box AF60)
      - Car and Truck Buying Made Easier, 1988-1993 (Box AF60)
      - Collateral literature, 1989-1996, (2 folders) (Box AF60)
      - Mustang, 1997 (Box AF60)
  - Fortune Magazine
    - Cover, 1984 Feb. 6 (Box AF60)
  - Frito-Lay
    - Case study and sweepstakes, undated, (2 folders) (Box AF60)
    - Plugging into the Power of Kids, undated (Box AF60)
  - Gap
    - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box AF60)
  - Gatorade
    - Hoop It Up, coaches fulfillment mailing, 1995 (Box AF60)
  - G.D. Searle
    - Case history, circa 1983 (Box AF60)
  - General Cigar
    - Case study and strategy, 1979-1981 (Box AF60)
  - General Electric Medical Systems
    - Seriographic presentation, undated (Box AF61)
  - General Foods
    - International Coffee, 1996-1997 (Box AF61)
  - Genus Credit Management
    - Account information, undated (Box AF61)
    - Brochure, 1999 (Box AF61)
    - Classified advertising, 1999 (Box AF61)
    - Journey of Fergus (educational series), 1999 (Box AF61)
    - Mail campaign, 1999 (Box AF61)
    - Made/Missed payment postcards, 1998 (Box AF61)
    - Newsletters, 1998-1999 (Box AF61)
    - Survey response cards, 1998 (Box AF61)
    - Welcome mailings, 1998-1999 (Box AF61)
    - Yellow Pages advertising, 1999-2000 (Box AF61)
  - Geocities
    - Advertising, undated (Box AF61)
  - Geo Magazine
    - Launch creative, 1998 (Box AF61)
  - Gevalia Kaffe
    - Acquisition, special offers, mailings, 1983-1995 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF61)
    - Brand overview, 1994 (Box AF61)
    - Brochures, undated (Box AF61)
    - Business review, rollout expansion plans, 1985 (Box AF61)
    - Case studies, undated (Box AF61)
    - Direct marketing sample book, 1997, (3 folders) (Box AF62)
    - Import Service posting, 1986 (Box AF62)
    - Incentives, undated (Box AF62)
    - Interview with Jan-Öjvind Swahn, undated (Box AF62)
    - Janevelope sample book, 1997 (Box AF62)
    - Marketing strategies, 1996 (Box AF62)
    - Mailings, 1983-1996, (4 folders) (Box AF62)
    - PIP sample book, 1997 (Box AF63)
    - Posters, 1995 (Box AF63)
    - Reports, 1986-1993 (Box AF63)
    - Trial shipment form, 1997 (Box AF63)
  - Grand Bay Hotel (Miami)
    - Creative (English and Spanish), 1997 (Box AF63)
  - Great Indoors
    - Store opening and creative, 1998 (Box AF63)
  - Grolier Enterprises
    - Book of Knowledge, 1979-1987, (4 folders) (Box AF63)
    - Building the Grolier Encyclopedia Business Through Curriculum Persuasion, 1986 (Box AF63)
    - Children's books (Let's Talk About Teasing, Teach Me About Mealtime), 1982-1984 (Box AF63)
    - NBK (New Book of Knowledge) communication evaluation (report by Kennan Research and Consulting), 1987 (Box AF64)
    - Top-Line presentation (by Polaris Research Associates), 1986 (Box AF64)
  - Groupe Danone
    - Creative, 1996-1997 (Box AF64)
  - Guinness
    - Bass Ale/Titanic movie tie-in, 1996 (Box AF64)
    - Black & Tan advertising, undated (Box AF64)
    - Case study, undated (Box AF64)
    - Creative, 1996-1998, (2 folders) (Box AF64)
    - World Record Toast, 1997 (Box AF64)
  - H&R Block (Chicago)
    - Case study, 1997 (Box AF64)
    - Mailings, 1996-1997 (Box AF64)
  - Hartz
    - Creative, undated (Box AF64)
  - Heath Bar (Chicago)
    - Take a Movie Break, 1993 (Box AF64)
  - Heinz
    - Agency assignment briefing, 1990 (Box AF64)
  - Henry's End Restaurant
    - Wild Game Festival, undated (Box AF64)
  - Hill's Pet Products (Science Diet)
    - Brochures, 1988-1990 and undated (Box AF64)
    - Case studies, 1987-1991, (2 folders) (Box AF64)
    - Creative (English and French), 1987-1993 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF64)
    - Printed material, undated (Box AF64)
  - Historic Preservation
    - Catalog, 1981 (Box AF65)
    - Invitation to membership, undated (Box AF65)
  - Holiday Inn Business Center
    - Creative and case study, 1989 (Box AF65)
    - Printed material, undated (Box AF65)
  - Hospital Corporation of America (HCA)
    - Advertising, undated (Box AF65)
    - Health plans, 1985 (Box AF65)
  - Hyatt
    - Brochures, 1992-1993 (Box AF65)
    - Case studies, 1988-1990 (Box AF65)
    - Frequent Flyer/Mileage Plus, 1992 (Box AF65)
    - Gold Passport/At Leisure, 1993 (Box AF65)
    - Mailers, 1992-1993, (3 folders) (Box AF65)
    - Printed material, 1992 (Box AF65)
  - IBM
    - CAD System and Health Care, undated (Box AF65)
    - Catalogs, 1984-1988, (1-2 of 4 folders) (Box AF65)
    - Catalogs, 1984-1988 (continued), (3-4 of 4 folders) (Box AF66)
    - Creative, undated (Box AF66)
    - Energy Perspective, undated (Box AF66)
    - Facts Court management, 1998 (Box AF66)
    - Human Kind deep computing, 1998 (Box AF66)
    - Mailers, 1984-1985 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF66)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986-1998 (Box AF66)
    - Printed materials
      - Connections, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Records Manager, 1999 (Box AF66)
  - InCharge Institute
    - Website, 1999-2000 (Box AF66)
  - Interactive Channel
    - Information, 1996 (Box AF66)
  - Jaguar (England)
    - Jaguar XJ creative and case study, 1995 (Box AF66)
  - Johnson & Johnson
    - Case studies and clippings, 1979-1992 and undated, (1 of 2 folders) (Box AF66)
    - Case studies and clippings, 1979-1992 and undated (continued), (2 of 2 folders) (Box AF67)
    - Child Development
      - Products marketing plan, 1981 (Box AF67)
      - Toy Retail Communications Plan, circa 1980 (Box AF67)
      - Mailers, 1978-1984 (Box AF67)
      - Miscellaneous creative, 1982-1986 (Box AF67)
  - Kendall-Futuro
    - Curity bladder control products, 1988 (Box AF67)
    - Mailer, 1987 (Box AF67)
  - Kessler Exchange
    - Information and Enrollment Form, undated (Box AF67)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box AF67)
  - Kodak
    - Articles, 1993-1994 (Box AF67)
    - Case studies, 1990 and undated (Box AF67)
    - Incentives and sales, undated (Box AF67)
    - Kodak For You action marketing program, 1994 (Box AF67)
    - Kolorkins Toys multi-brand promotion, 1989 (Box AF67)
    - Miscellaneous Creative, undated (Box AF67)
    - Presentation Power, 1990 (Box AF67)
    - Product advertisements, undated (Box AF68)
    - Report1987 (Box AF68)
    - Reports and clippings, 1987-1993, (2 folders) (Box AF68)
    - Sample file, 1986 (Box AF68)
    - Targeted Franchise Marketing (TFM), 1986-1988, (3 folders) (Box AF68)
    - Targeted Franchise Marketing Results Update, 1990 (Box AF69)
    - Target Relationship Marketing, undated (Box AF69)
    - Target Relationship Marketing Presentation, undated (Box AF69)
  - Kraft Foods
    - Co-marketing program with H.E. Buff, 1995 (Box AF69)
    - International non-media channels, 1996 (Box AF69)
    - Case studies, 1992-1997 (Box AF69)
    - Kraft Foods/Kroger Atlanta--Football Fever campaign, 1994 (Box AF69)
  - Liberty Travel, Inc.
    - American Airlines catalogs, 1991-1992 (Box AF69)
    - Princess Cruises catalog, 1991-1992 (Box AF69)
  - L. L. Bean
    - Esquire Magazine advertising, 1982 (Box AF69)
    - Guide to Fitness, 1985 (Box AF69)
    - Ordering catalogs, 1975-1988, (3 folders) (Box AF69)
    - Presentation, 1986 (Box AF69)
    - Report and miscellaneous, 1978-1987 (Box AF69)
  - L' Oreal
    - Biotherm Skin Care, 1988 (Box AF70)
    - Case study, circa 1985 (Box AF70)
    - Pantene
      - Mailers, undated (Box AF70)
      - Packaging, undated (Box AF70)
  - Lucent Technologies
    - Client letters, 1996-1997 (Box AF70)
  - Macromedia
    - Director commercial mailing, 1996-1997 (Box AF70)
  - Manufacturers Hanover
    - Advertisements, 1985-1986 (Box AF70)
    - Letters of Information, 1986-1987 (Box AF70)
    - Reports, 1982-1986 (Box AF70)
  - Merck(Propecia)
    - Creative, 1998 (Box AF70)
    - Retention program, 1998 (Box AF70)
  - Merrill Lynch
    - Cash Management Account (CMA) program information, undated (Box AF70)
    - CMA interest forms and information, 1983-1985 (Box AF70)
    - CMA referral form, 1982 (Box AF71)
    - Equity Access credit account, undated (Box AF71)
    - Information form, undated (Box AF71)
    - Mailers, 1985 (Box AF71)
    - Market letters, undated (Box AF71)
    - Personalized Financial Pathfinder, 1983 (Box AF71)
    - Reports and presentations, 1981-1985 (Box AF71)
    - Sharebuilder client accounts, 1986 (Box AF71)
    - Speeches by William Waters, circa 1983 (Box AF71)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance
    - Early Curriculum Execution, undated (Box AF71)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art
    - Christmas catalog, 1982 (Box AF71)
  - MichCon
    - Home Comfort Solutions, 1997 (Box AF71)
    - Michigan Consolidated Gas Co. Home Protection PLUS, 1988 (Box AF71)
    - Website, undated (Box AF71)
    - Website Request, 1998 (Box AF71)
  - Michigan Bell
    - Yellow Pages advertisers, 1983 (Box AF71)
  - Microsoft
    - Catalog (Spanish), 1996 (Box AF71)
    - Developers, 1995 (Box AF71)
    - Latin American case studies, 1996 (Box AF71)
    - MORGS, 1995 (Box AF71)
    - Newsletters, 1995-1996 (Box AF71)
  - Miller Brewing Co.
    - Case studies, 1993-1885 (Box AF71)
    - Creative, 1993-1995, (2 folders) (Box AF71)
    - Direct Marketing case studies, 1994 (Box AF71)
    - Genuine Team, 1994 (Box AF71)
    - Mailersm 1993-1994 (Box AF72)
    - Miller Time Card program, 1993 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF72)
    - Reports, 1992-1994, (2 folders) (Box AF72)
    - Sports Marketing Promotions, undated (Box AF72)
    - Sports Marketing Promotions: Chicago Bulls/White Sox, 1993-1995 (Box AF72)
    - Survey, undated (Box AF72)
    - WCJ account summary, 1992 (Box AF72)
  - Mobil Chemical
    - Films Division, undated (Box AF72)
  - Monro Muffler (Hutchins/Y&R)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995-1996 (Box AF72)
  - Monroe Community College
    - Creative (Hutchins/Y&R), 1997 (Box AF72)
  - Monsanto
    - Case study, undated (Box AF72)
  - Nabisco (Knox Nutra Joint)
    - Creative, 1998-1999 (Box AF72)
  - National Consumer Photo Census
    - Survey, 1986 (Box AF72)
  - National Foundation for Consumer Credit
    - Newspaper advertising, 1999 (Box AF72)
  - National Rife Association of America
    - Information on NRA, 1990-1991 (Box AF73)
    - Magazines, 1989-1990 (Box AF73)
    - Membership letters, 1990-1991, (3 folders) (Box AF73)
    - Premium Pak, 1991 (Box AF73)
  - Nationwide Insurance(San Francisco)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box AF73)
  - New York Telephone
    - Miscellaneous, 1980-1982 and undated (Box AF73)
    - NYNEX, 1984 (Box AF73)
  - Nintendo
    - Miscellaneous, 1994-1995 (Box AF74)
  - No Nonsense Pantyhose(Chicago)
    - Case studies, 1991 (Box AF74)
  - Novell (WCJ San Francisco)
    - Netware 4.1 campaign, 1996 (Box AF74)
  - Operation Welcome Home
    - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box AF74)
  - Orangina
    - Case study, 1995 (Box AF74)
  - Pan Am
    - Creative, 1982-1985, (5 folders) (Box AF74)
  - Partnership for Improved Air Travel
    - Mailer, 1988 (Box AF74)
  - Pepsi
    - P.R.O.F.I.T.S. Manual, 1993, (3 folders) (Box AF75)
  - Pertoleum Heat & Power
    - Print advertising, undated (Box AF75)
  - Phoenix House
    - Creative, 1982-1983 (Box AF75)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982-1984, (2 folders) (Box AF75)
    - Slide Presentation Script, 1983 (Box AF75)
  - Phillip Morris (Parliament)
    - Creative, 1999 (Box AF75)
  - P. J. Carroll
    - Creative, 1988, (2 folders) (Box AF75)
  - Porsche
    - Direct Marketing article, 1989 (Box AF76)
  - Prescription Club of America
    - Mail, undated (Box AF76)
  - Prodigy
    - Creative, undated (Box AF76)
  - Proctor & Gamble
    - Creative, 1979 and undated (Box AF76)
    - Oil of Olay, 1985-1986 (Box AF76)
    - Pampers, Pert, Swap N Save, circa 1980s (Box AF76)
  - Profina
    - Budget Worksheet and Brochures, undated (Box AF76)
    - Paper and envelope, undated (Box AF76)
  - Quaker Oats
    - Gatorade case Study, undated (Box AF76)
  - Quicken Insurance
    - Creative, 2000 (Box AF76)
  - Reader's Digest
    - Creative, undated (Box AF76)
  - Richardson-Vicks
    - Pantene case Ssudy, circa 1985 (Box AF76)
    - Tempo antacid, Pantene1985-1986 (Box AF76)
  - Roche Laboratories(NY)
    - Rocephin mailer, 1998 (Box AF76)
  - Save the Children
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1983 (Box AF76)
  - Schiefflin & Somerset
    - Classic Malts of Scotland creative, 1997 (Box AF76)
  - Sears
    - Best Customer Program Welcome Kit Mailing, undated (Box AF76)
    - Building Relatioships Builds Profits (Sears Home Services), undated (Box AF76)
    - Building the Value Proposition of the Sears Card, 1997 (Box AF76)
    - Case studies, 1994-1997, and undated (Box AF76)
    - Creative, 1994-1999 (Box AF76)
    - Gilda's Club, 1996 (Box AF76)
    - Home Central Communications Guidelines, 1997 (Box AF76)
    - Mailers, 1995 (Box AF77)
    - Sears Charge creative, 1991 (Box AF77)
    - Shop at Home, 1984 (Box AF77)
  - Sheraton
    - Creative, 1985-1986 (Box AF77)
  - Showtime
    - Case studies and creative, 1990-1996 (Box AF77)
    - Mailers, 1989-1993 (Box AF77)
    - Overview presentation, 1996 (Box AF77)
    - Reports, 1994-1995 (Box AF77)
    - Reports and memoranda, 1991 (Box AF77)
  - Simon & Schuster
    - Ronald Reagan, Speaking my Mind mailers, 1989 (Box AF77)
  - Smith Kline Beecham
    - Ecotrin--Ecotrin Report (Vol. 2, Issue 1), 1998 (Box AF77)
    - Nicorette--Committed Quitters campaign, 1996-1997 (Box AF77)
    - Tums creative, undated (Box AF77)
  - Sony
    - Home Entertainment competitive, 2000-2001, (3 folders) (Box AF78)
    - Creative, 1982-1982 (Box AF78)
    - (Miami/Mexico)Spanish--Language creative/case study for Latin American market, 1995-1996 (Box AF78)
    - Financial ServicesStudent Moniter--Lifestyle & Media Highlights, 2000 (Box AF78)
    - xPlod creative, 2000 (Box AF78)
  - Spiegel
    - General, 1978-1984 (Box AF79)
    - Creative, 1979-1980 (Box AF79)
  - Sports Illustrated
    - Creative and miscellaneous, 1982-1993 (Box AF79)
    - Reports, 1987-1992 (Box AF79)
  - Starmedia
    - Case study, undated (Box AF79)
  - Stayfree
    - Reports, 1992 and undated (Box AF79)
  - Stone & Adler
    - Creative and miscellaneous, 1983-1985 (Box AF79)
  - Sunkist(Chicago)
    - Case study, undated (Box AF79)
  - Sunsoft(Chicago)
    - (Video Games) Tie-in campaign, undated (Box AF79)
  - Suzuki
    - Circuit City Swepstakes, undated (Box AF79)
  - Swiss Air
    - Creative, 1997 (Box AF79)
  - Swiss Colony
    - Creative, 1981-1985, (2 folders) (Box AF79)
  - Taco Bell
    - Case studies, 1991-1996 (Box AF80)
    - Creative, 1991-1998, (2 folders) (Box AF80)
    - Display signs, 1993-1994 (Box AF80)
    - Enter Marketing Manual, undated (Box AF80)
    - Frequent Rewards Club, 1994 (Box AF80)
    - Loyalty Component of Capturing Lifetime Value, 1993 (Box AF80)
    - Memoranda and miscellaneous, 1994-1997 (Box AF80)
    - Reports, 1996 and undated (Box AF80)
    - Rocky & Bullwinkle promotion, 1993 (Box AF80)
    - Star Wars tie-in cups, 1997 (Box AF80)
    - WCJ Newport Beach--Value Initiative background, 1994 (Box AF80)
  - Tasco(Miami)
    - National Audobon Society brochure, 1999 (Box AF80)
  - Thirteen (PBS)
    - Creative, 1988-1989 (Box AF81)
    - Mailers, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box AF81)
    - Mailers--Club 13, 1988-1989 (Box AF81)
    - Not By Wunderman, 1988-1989 (Box AF81)
  - Thomas Garraway
    - General, 1986-1988 (Box AF81)
    - Mailers, 1986-1988, (2 folders) (Box AF81)
    - Printed material, 1986 (Box AF81)
  - Time, Inc.
    - Creative, 1975-1990 (Box AF82)
    - Time Plus mailing, 1989-1990 (Box AF82)
  - Time-Life Books
    - American Country, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box AF82)
    - Case studies, 1981-1987 (Box AF82)
    - Clippings, 1985 (Box AF82)
    - Creative, 1976-1990, (4 folders) (Box AF82)
    - Discover Magazine, undated (Box AF82)
    - The Enchanted World & Mystic Places, 1985-1988 (Box AF82)
    - Home Repair & Improvement, 1985-1990 (Box AF83)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980-1995 (Box AF83)
    - Suspense!, undated (Box AF83)
    - Time Warner and Wunderman Cato Johnson, 1992 (Box AF83)
    - The Vietnam Experience, 1989 (Box AF83)
    - Voyage Through The Universe, 1989-1990 (Box AF83)
    - World War 2 (The Great Warbirds/The Third Reich), 1979-1987 (Box AF83)
    - What Works in Subscription Acquisition, 1995 (Box AF83)
  - Tissot, Inc.
    - Mail, undated (Box AF83)
  - Tops Friendly Market
    - Case studies and miscellaneous, 1993-1996 (Box AF83)
    - Presentations (Hutchins/Y&R), 1992 (Box AF83)
  - Trans World Airlines
    - Creative, 1986, (2 folders) (Box AF83)
    - Mailers, 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box AF83)
  - Union Carbide
    - Mailer, circa 1986 (Box AF84)
  - United Airlines(Mosaica, NY)
    - Creative [English and Japanese], 1997 (Box AF84)
  - USA Today
    - Complementary Subscription, undated (Box AF84)
  - US Army/Army ROTC
    - Campaign photographs, 1994 (Box AF84)
    - Acquisition to male seniors, 1989 (Box AF84)
    - Army Nursing Program mailing, circa 1990 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF84)
    - Army Reserve mailers to veterans, 1988 (Box AF84)
    - Army Reserve retention planner, 1988-1989 (Box AF84)
    - Case studies, 1993 and undated (Box AF84)
    - College benefits mailers, 1989-1999 (Box AF84)
    - Information kit, 1996 (Box AF84)
    - JROTC Building a Better School and Better Students, 1994 (Box AF84)
    - Mailers, 1989-1999 and undated, (1-2 of 8 folders) (Box AF84)
    - Mailers, 1989-1999 and undated (continued), (3-8 of 8 folders) (Box AF85)
    - ROTC brochures, 1996-1997 (Box AF85)
  - USPS
    - Case studies, 1990-1997 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF85)
    - Communications review, 1994 (Box AF85)
    - Creative, 1994-1998, and undated (Box AF86)
    - Holiday promotion, circa 1993 (Box AF86)
    - Imagitas-Mover's guide, 1999 (Box AF86)
    - Inbound scripts, 1995 (Box AF86)
    - Manual of Direct Mail, circa 1995 (Box AF86)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994-1994, and undated (Box AF86)
    - Package Services campaign launch, 1997 (Box AF86)
    - Printed material, 1993-1994 (Box AF86)
    - Profit Connection, 1997 (Box AF86)
    - Report: PTT Post Holland case history on the promotion of direct mail since 1982circa 1985 (Box AF86)
    - Smart Solutions, 1995 (Box AF86)
  - United Way of Greater Rochester(Hutchins/Y&R)
    - Case study, 1994 (Box AF86)
  - Viewdata Corporation
    - Viewtron, 1982-1983 (Box AF86)
  - Warner-Lambert (CERTS)Chicago
    - Case studies and briefs, 1992-1993 (Box AF86)
    - Comic Relief presentation, 1992 (Box AF86)
  - Wells Fargo
    - Creative, 1989, 1997 (Box AF87)
  - Weight Watchers
    - Creative, 1989-1992 (Box AF87)
    - Print advertising, undated (Box AF87)
    - Summary report, 1988 (Box AF87)
  - WNET/Thirteen
    - Membership drive, 1989 (Box AF87)
  - WCJ
    - Mailers, 1986-1994 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF87)